asiankisses.de 2012-11-09

# Asian Kisses

|  | | |   
---|---|---  
|  |    
  
---  
IK Softwareportal GmbH is the operator of Asian Kisses.

IK Softwareportal GmbH takes your privacy seriously and is constantly striving to raise all personal data in accordance with the applicable data protection law and to use. IK Softwareportal GmbH would like to explain the basis of this privacy policy, which data is absolutely needed and how you can gain by specifying additional, optional data, additional benefits. Your information is collected and stored if you have given us your consent.

Changes to data protection provisions that affect the processing of your personal information, we will notify you by e-mail. If you do not agree with the latest version, so you have the opportunity to withdraw your consent within four weeks. During this time, the changes have no effect.

## 1\. Personal information that we need to deliver our services

If you want to use IK Softwareportal GmbH as a pure information site without registration, we do not require and collect any personal information from you. But if you want to take advantage the mediation services of IK Softwareportal GmbH , you must register on our site. During registration, we ask the following information from you: name, e-mail address, address (optional), date of birth. In addition, you must answer a series of personal questions that allow us to create your partner proposal.

For your security, all issues are identified, the answers to other members will not be displayed. The answers to all other questions will be displayed to other members if necessary.

## 2\. Termination of your membership (removal of your profile)

You have the option to stop receiving correspondence from **Asian Kisses** at any time you choose.  
Options are:  

  * You find an OPT-OUT link in every email you receive from us at the bottom of the email.
  * When you are logged in at the site you go to menu "My membership". There you find a button to delete your profile.
  * Send us an e-mail to **_[info@asiankisses.de](mailto:info@asiankisses.de?subject=Questions%20for%20Asian%20Kisses)_** to let us know that you would like to opt out of future correspondence and we will remove you from our lists.
  * Send us a fax to +49 911 308 44 77 844 with your email address you used to register at Asian Kisses and your member ID ****

## 3\. Use of your data required for registration

After termination of the contract, all data from the member from IK Softwareportal GmbH will be deleted unless there is special need for storage.

## 4\. Advanced data collection, storage and processing to create a personal profile

Grant IK Softwareportal GmbH also consent to collect more voluntary data for individual information and support to use and process, IK Softwareportal GmbH will use this personal information only for such purposes. Also, this consent is recorded by IK Softwareportal GmbH.  
Some services provided by IK Softwareportal GmbH are offered in cooperation with partner companies. Unless you want to take advantage of these services, you need to register separately with each party. IK Softwareportal GmbH to ensure the selection of partners that the data protection provisions are observed when the partners in order to protect your personal data.

## 5\. Type of data analysis

IK Softwareportal GmbH will do analysis of the behavior of users on the IK Softwareportal GmbH pages. This is happening against the background that IK Softwareportal GmbH would like to improve its services continuously. These evaluations are not personal, but are conducted anonymously.

## 6\. Use of Cookies

IK Softwareportal GmbH uses so-called "cookies" to each participant with the best possible individually tailored offer to him and allow him to provide convenient use of the service. A cookie is a text file, either temporarily in the computer ("session" cookie) or on the hard drive ("persistent cookie") is stored. Cookies contain e.g. Information about previous requests of a subscriber to the server or information on what offers he has been called. IK Softwareportal GmbH uses "session cookies", affiliate cookies and persistent cookies.

### (a) Session Cookies

IK Softwareportal GmbH uses mostly "session cookies". These are not stored on the hard disk of the participant, but are deleted when you close the browser. "Session cookies" are used here for load-balancing (balancing the system load) and for tracking click streams.

### (b) Permanent Cookies

IK Softwareportal GmbH uses "persistent cookies" to your personal settings (such as sorting lists) to store the subscriber, the service excellent, and align it to the login authentication. The cookies prevent the participant must be set in subsequent visits, the IK Softwareportal GmbH web site his personal settings again. In addition, cookies can be based on the example automatically , has to determine which Member State of the participants, whether he received certain information / offers, or has participated in a survey. In addition, use the service, which has commissioned IK Softwareportal GmbH with the analysis of user behavior, permanent cookies to recognize repeat users can. These services store the data transmitted from the cookie identifies you. An assignment to the IP address of the participant is not held.

### (c) Affiliate-Cookies

Furthermore, IK Softwareportal GmbH uses cookies when a subscriber accesses an external advertising space on the service from IK Softwareportal GmbH. These cookies are used to settle accounts with the cooperation partners and do not contain personal data of the participant. They are automatically deleted after a period of 4 weeks.

### (d) Deleting of Cookies

The participant always has the option to reject the cookie insert. This is usually done by selecting the appropriate option in your browser settings or additional programs. Exact details of the help function in the browser of the participant read. The participant decides against the use of cookies, this may reduce the scope of services and may have negative impact of the services of IK Softwareportal GmbH.

## 7.Information about stored data

According to § 34 of the Data Protection Act we will give you very much free and in writing information about your saved personal data. Please fax us a copy of both parallel sides of your identity card, so that we can determine your unique identity. Thank you.

## 8\. For more information on Privacy

Please remember what you should do whenever you voluntarily provide personal information online (eg in chat rooms, e-mail, forums), this information may be collected and used by others. So you might receive unsolicited messages from others when you send in areas with public access personal information online. They act cautiously and responsibly online and pay attention to the secrecy of your passwords and / or other personal information. If you have forgotten your password, click here and enter your login in the box or e-mail address. If you click "Send Password", you will receive the link to enter a password / change password immediately by e-mail.

## 9\. Self-control

IK Softwareportal GmbH allows compliance with the Privacy Policy regularly checked by an independent data protection officer. Please contact with any questions about privacy on our first customer. If your privacy questions could not be satisfactorily resolved by the customer, you can also contact our data security consultant Mr. Ingo Legner. You can reach him at: **[info@derschild.de](mailto:info@derschild.de?subject=Privacy%20request%20for%20Asian%20Kisses)** . 

## 1\. Content

The author reserves the right not to be responsible for the topicality, correctness, completeness or quality of the information provided. Liability claims regarding damage caused by the use of any information provided, including any kind of information which is incomplete or incorrect,will therefore be rejected.  
All offers are not-binding and without obligation. Parts of the pages or the complete publication including all offers and information might be extended, changed or partly or completely deleted by the author without separate announcement. 

## 2\. Referrals and links

The author is not responsible for any contents linked or referred to from his pages - unless he has full knowledge of illegal contents and would be able to prevent the visitors of his site fromviewing those pages. If any damage occurs by the use of information presented there, only the author of the respective pages might be liable, not the one who has linked to these pages. Furthermore the author is not liable for any postings or messages published by users of discussion boards, guestbooks or mailinglists provided on his page. 

## 3\. Copyright

The author intended not to use any copyrighted material for the publication or, if not possible, to indicate the copyright of the respective object. The copyright for any material created by the author is reserved. Any duplication or use of objects such as images, diagrams, sounds or texts in other electronic or printed publications is not permitted without the author's agreement. 

## 4\. Legal validity of this disclaimer

This disclaimer is to be regarded as part of the internet publication which you were referred from. If sections or individual terms of this statement are not legal or correct, the content or validity of the other parts remain uninfluenced by this fact.   
| | | |   
Hotel Thailand | | Learn Tagalog Filipino | Learn Thai | Learn Chinese|  | Freeware|  | Languages|  | Privacy Policy|  | Terms of service  
---|---|---|---|---|---
